David Stick Papers PC.5001
State Archives of North Carolina
- Personal Papers, 1907-2009 and undated; 45074; 0.610; Stick, David, 1919-2009
  - Other Personal Papers, 1922-2009 and undated; 6729; Stick, David, 1919-2009
    - Prospectus for the Lords Proprietors' Colony, Colington Island, North Carolina, 1964; 28628; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Prospectus for the Lords Proprietors' Colony, Colington Island, North Carolina)
    - Radio and Television Appearances, circa 1940s-1998; 7387; Stick, David, 1919-2009
      - WRAL Broadcast (First Broadcast) [Glass Transcription Disc], circa 1940s; 190879; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item WRAL Broadcast (First Broadcast) [Glass Transcription Disc])
      - North Carolina This Week, UNC-TV [audiocassette], 1 June 1973; 190694; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item North Carolina This Week, UNC-TV [audiocassette])
      - "Media Center" Radio Interview, Regional Library [audiocassette], 2 August 1973; 190695; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item "Media Center" Radio Interview, Regional Library [audiocassette])
      - Bob Lacy WBT Radio Charlotte [audiocassette], 21 February 1974; 190696; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item Bob Lacy WBT Radio Charlotte [audiocassette])
      - David Stick Interview UNC-TV Ch. 2 [audiocassette], 26 March 1974; 190697; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item David Stick Interview UNC-TV Ch. 2 [audiocassette])
      - N.C. News Conference [audiocassette], 1 June 1974; 190698; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item N.C. News Conference [audiocassette])
      - Coastal Resources Commission and CAMA, WOBR Radio [audiocassette], 10 October 1974; 190699; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item Coastal Resources Commission and CAMA, WOBR Radio [audiocassette])
      - David Stick - TV Ed. Network N.C. News Conference [audiocassette], circa 1974; 190700; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item David Stick - TV Ed. Network N.C. News Conference [audiocassette])
      - Water Bond Referendum, WOBR Radio [audiocassette], 11 April 1975; 190701; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item Water Bond Referendum, WOBR Radio [audiocassette])
      - Conversation - David Stick and Parker Chesson, WVEC-TV 13 [audiocassette], 13 April 1975; 190702; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item Conversation - David Stick and Parker Chesson, WVEC-TV 13 [audiocassette])
      - David Stick - Interview by Bill Friday, North Carolina People [audiocassette], 26 September 1976; 190703; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item David Stick - Interview by Bill Friday, North Carolina People [audiocassette])
      - Newsmakers, WTAR-TV 3 [audiocassette], 30 July 1978; 190704; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item Newsmakers, WTAR-TV 3 [audiocassette])
      - Beyond the Breakers, UNC-TV [audiocassette], 23 July 1980; 190705; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item Beyond the Breakers, UNC-TV [audiocassette])
      - Paradox in Paradise, UNC-TV [audiocassette], 19 November 1980; 190706; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item Paradox in Paradise, UNC-TV [audiocassette])
      - North Carolina Lighthouses: Romance and Reality, Channel 7, Washington, NC [audiocassette], 12 July 1981; 190707; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item North Carolina Lighthouses: Romance and Reality, Channel 7, Washington, NC [audiocassette])
      - In Search of the Lost Colony (Nationally Syndicated) [audiocassette], 1981; 190708; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item In Search of the Lost Colony (Nationally Syndicated) [audiocassette])
      - North Carolina People (Bill Friday) UNC-TV [audiocassette], 1982; 190709; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item North Carolina People (Bill Friday) UNC-TV [audiocassette])
      - WOBR Live, Outer Banks Community Foundation [audiocassette], 18 July 1983; 190710; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item WOBR Live, Outer Banks Community Foundation [audiocassette])
      - Hospitality House - Hurricanes, TV-7 Washington, NC [audiocassette], 31 July 1983; 190711; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item Hospitality House - Hurricanes, TV-7 Washington, NC [audiocassette])
      - Hospitality House - Outer Banks Community Foundation, TV-7 Washington, NC [audiocassette], 12 November 1983; 190712; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item Hospitality House - Outer Banks Community Foundation, TV-7 Washington, NC [audiocassette])
      - North Carolina People, Interview by Jake Dunlop, TV-2 [audiocassette], 25 June 1984; 190713; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item North Carolina People, Interview by Jake Dunlop, TV-2 [audiocassette])
      - Library Legislation, WGAI Radio [audiocassette], 11 July 1985; 190714; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item Library Legislation, WGAI Radio [audiocassette])
      - North Carolina People: Elizabeth II, Fort Raleigh, Elizabethan Gardens [VHS], 1984; 190880; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item North Carolina People: Elizabeth II, Fort Raleigh, Elizabethan Gardens [VHS])
      - The Ash Wednesday Storm: Interview with Elizabeth Smith, David Stick, Ann Marlette, etc. [VHS], April 1987; 190881; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item The Ash Wednesday Storm: Interview with Elizabeth Smith, David Stick, Ann Marlette, etc. [VHS])
      - Hurricane '87 WVEC-TV13 [VHS], 5 September 1987; 190882; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item Hurricane '87 WVEC-TV13 [VHS])
      - Growth on the Outer Banks WTKR-TV3 [VHS], 1987; 190883; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item Growth on the Outer Banks WTKR-TV3 [VHS])
      - Graveyard of the Atlantic WTKR-TV3 [VHS], [1987?]; 190884; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item Graveyard of the Atlantic WTKR-TV3 [VHS])
      - Moving the Cape Hatteras Lighthouse, CNN (Segment Aired 53-56 Minutes into the Newscast) [VHS], 25 June 1989; 190885; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item Moving the Cape Hatteras Lighthouse, CNN (Segment Aired 53-56 Minutes into the Newscast) [VHS])
      - Our Battered Coast/As the Seasons Change segments from WFMY-TV [VHS], circa 1993; 190886; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item Our Battered Coast/As the Seasons Change segments from WFMY-TV [VHS])
      - Shipwrecks - The G.A. Kohler, Carolina Country, TV10 [VHS], 1993; 190887; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item Shipwrecks - The G.A. Kohler, Carolina Country, TV10 [VHS])
      - North Carolina Now, UNC-TV (Ditch Hatch Brief Interview with David Stick on CAMA) [VHS], 27 September 1994; 190888; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item North Carolina Now, UNC-TV (Ditch Hatch Brief Interview with David Stick on CAMA) [VHS])
      - Cape Hatteras Lighthouse Call-In Program on UNC-TV with Geneva Perry [VHS], 21 April 1998; 190889; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item Cape Hatteras Lighthouse Call-In Program on UNC-TV with Geneva Perry [VHS])
    - Reassessment of North Carolina Government, 1981-1982; 28629; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Reassessment of North Carolina Government)
    - Respass, Chris and Tammy, 1978-1981; 28630; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Respass, Chris and Tammy)
    - Respass, Lin and Tucker, 1987-1989; 28631; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Respass, Lin and Tucker)
    - Roanoke Island Research Project, 1981; 28632; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Roanoke Island Research Project)
    - Robbins, Johnny (Manteo High School), 1975-1976; 28633; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Robbins, Johnny (Manteo High School))
    - Rock Church, 1974-1975; 28634; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Rock Church)
    - Rock Church - Sale, 1981; 28635; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Rock Church - Sale)
    - School Bond Fact Sheet, 1988; 28636; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder School Bond Fact Sheet)
    - Schools - Bond Issue, 1988; 28637; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Schools - Bond Issue)
    - Schools - Fletcher and Geneva, 1998; 28638; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Schools - Fletcher and Geneva)
    - Sears, Dr. Roger, 2005; 28639; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Sears, Dr. Roger)
    - Senter, Jim, 2006; 28640; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Senter, Jim)
    - Storytelling: Outer Banks Memories [DVD], 26 March 2007; 190739; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Item Storytelling: Outer Banks Memories [DVD])
    - Town of Manteo Waterfront Development Project [3 folders], 1999-2000; 28641; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Town of Manteo Waterfront Development Project [3 folders])
    - Transcript of Interview with David Stick, 2007; 28642; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Transcript of Interview with David Stick)
    - U.S. Marine Corps Combat Correspondents Association Annual Convention, 1967-1970; 28643; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder U.S. Marine Corps Combat Correspondents Association Annual Convention)
    - Waldrop, Grayson, 1996-2004; 28644; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Waldrop, Grayson)
    - Workshop - County and Towns, 7 May 1985; 28645; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Workshop - County and Towns)
    - Wright Brothers National Memorial Management Objectives Workshop, 1994; 28646; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Wright Brothers National Memorial Management Objectives Workshop)
    - Wright Memorial: Trees, 1996-1998; 39377; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Wright Memorial: Trees)
    - Year 2000 - Bortz, 1980; 28647; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Year 2000 - Bortz)
- Business Papers, 1910-1997 and undated; 45075; Stick, David, 1919-2009
  David Stick had numerous business interests, but he focused primarily on real estate and the book trade. This series contains records related to Stick's businesses. The Real Estate subseries of this series includes extensive documentation of the early development of various historical housing subdivisions on the Outer Banks, such as Virginia Dare Shores and Southern Shores. Included are records related to the land development company founded by Stick and his father Frank, the Kitty Hawk Land Company, as well as the real estate sales company led by Stick, Southern Shores Realty Company. The Kitty Hawk Land Company subseries includes several folders of architectural drawings and plans for Frank Stick's flat-top houses, a famous architectural feature of the Southern Shores area. Researchers should note that Stick frequently conducted business on behalf of both companies simultaneously, so papers related to Southern Shores Realty frequently appear in the Kitty Hawk Land Company files, and vice versa. Other real estate papers in this series include material related to the Kitty Hawk Shores Corporation, which was co-founded by Frank Stick in the 1920s to promote development along the Outer Banks; the Stear-Mark Corporation, for which David Stick served as a contractor in the late 1950s-early 1960s, and Stick's various licenses and other personal papers related to his real estate career.
  The Book Trade subseries contains records related to two bookselling businesses operated by Stick: David Stick, Bookman and North Carolina Books. Records in this subseries primarily consist of payroll and personnel records, correspondence with book dealers, catalogs, financial records, inventories and lists, and promotional material.
  Other businesses documented in this series include the Kitty Hawk Craft Shop, operated by Stick and his wife, Phyllis, in the early 1950s; Lewis and Clark Explorer Maps, Ltd., which Stick used to reproduce and sell copies of early North Carolina maps; Outer Banks Contractors; and the Southern Shores Motor Lodge.
  - Real Estate, 1926-1991 and undated; 6730; Stick, David, 1919-2009
    - Kitty Hawk Land Company, 1926-1985; 7026; Stick, David, 1919-2009
      - Addresses of Property Owners, 1949; 28648; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Addresses of Property Owners)
      - Avon Beach, 1926-1931; 28649; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Avon Beach)
      - Aydlett, Cyrus, Elizabeth City Finance Co., 1952-1954; 28650; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Aydlett, Cyrus, Elizabeth City Finance Co.)
      - Burrus, Speight, Management Study, circa 1972; 28651; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Burrus, Speight, Management Study)
      - Chicahauk, 1974; 28652; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Chicahauk)
      - Colington Tax List, 1954; 28653; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Colington Tax List)
      - Congressional, 1953-1967; 28654; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Congressional)
      - Credit Regulations (Federal Reserve), 1950-1951; 28655; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Credit Regulations (Federal Reserve))
      - Curran, Frank J., 1950; 28656; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Curran, Frank J.)
      - Current, 1955-1956; 28657; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Current)
      - Dare County Lands, 1952; 28658; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Dare County Lands)
      - David Stick Personal, 1969-1972; 28659; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder David Stick Personal)
      - Davis, Burke, 1964; 28660; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Davis, Burke)
      - Dayton Beach Property, 1950-1952; 28661; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Dayton Beach Property)
      - Deed Abstracts: Frank Stick, Grantor, circa 1950s; 28662; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Deed Abstracts: Frank Stick, Grantor)
      - Deed Abstracts: Miscellaneous Holdings, circa 1950s; 28663; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Deed Abstracts: Miscellaneous Holdings)
      - Deed Abstracts: Various [2 Folders], circa 1950s; 28664; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Deed Abstracts: Various [2 Folders])
      - Financial Statements, 1949-1953; 28665; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Financial Statements)
      - Financial Statements, 1954-1969; 28666; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Financial Statements)
      - Financial Statements, 1970; 28667; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Financial Statements)
      - Financial Statements, 1971; 28668; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Financial Statements)
      - Financial Statements, 1972; 28669; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Financial Statements)
      - Financial Statements [2 Folders], 1973; 28670; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Financial Statements [2 Folders])
      - Financial Statements [Folder 1 of 2], 1974; 28671; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Financial Statements [Folder 1 of 2])
      - Financial Statements [Folder 2 of 2], 1974; 28672; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Financial Statements [Folder 2 of 2])
      - Financial Statements, 1975; 28673; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Financial Statements)
      - Harrington, Jim, 1976; 28674; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Harrington, Jim)
      - Hatteras Holding Corporation, 1929-1953; 28675; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Hatteras Holding Corporation)
      - Helm, Robert Jr., 1951-1953; 28676; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Helm, Robert Jr.)
      - Home Planning: Rough Plans, 1947-1948; 28677; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Home Planning: Rough Plans)
      - House Plans (Rough Draft), circa 1940s; 28678; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder House Plans (Rough Draft))
      - Insurance, 1952-1953; 28679; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Insurance)
      - Kitty Hawk Beach and Kitty Hawk Woods Auction, 1966; 28680; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Kitty Hawk Beach and Kitty Hawk Woods Auction)
      - Lawrence, Harry, 1969; 28681; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Lawrence, Harry)
      - Lewis, C.C., 1949-1952; 28682; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Lewis, C.C.)
      - Loose Material Marked "Duplicates", 1965-1970; 28683; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Loose Material Marked "Duplicates")
      - Loose Papers, 1954-1970; 28684; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Loose Papers)
      - McCown and McCown, 1952-1953; 28685; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder McCown and McCown)
      - McMullan and Aydlett, 1952-1954; 28686; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder McMullan and Aydlett)
      - McMullan, J.B., 1957-1959; 28687; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder McMullan, J.B.)
      - Meekins/Dough/Stetson Agreement re: Land on Colington Island, 1955; 28688; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Meekins/Dough/Stetson Agreement re: Land on Colington Island)
      - Minutes: Preliminary Draft, Board of Directors, 1951-1969; 28689; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Minutes: Preliminary Draft, Board of Directors)
      - Minutes: Board of Directors, 1956-1970; 28690; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Minutes: Board of Directors)
      - Minutes: Preliminary Draft, Stockholders, 1967-1968; 28691; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Minutes: Preliminary Draft, Stockholders)
      - Minutes, 1970-1972; 28692; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Minutes)
      - Minutes: Board of Directors, 14 January 1972; 28693; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Minutes: Board of Directors)
      - Minutes: Board of Directors, 25 February 1972; 28694; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Minutes: Board of Directors)
      - Minutes: Board of Directors, 10 March 1972; 28695; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Minutes: Board of Directors)
      - Minutes: Board of Directors, 24 March 1972; 28696; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Minutes: Board of Directors)
      - Minutes: Board of Directors, 23 June 1972; 28697; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Minutes: Board of Directors)
      - Minutes: Board of Directors, 16 October 1972; 28698; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Minutes: Board of Directors)
      - Minutes: Board of Directors, 27 November 1972; 28699; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Minutes: Board of Directors)
      - Minutes: Board of Directors, 25 January 1973; 28700; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Minutes: Board of Directors)
      - Minutes: Board of Directors, 24 May 1973; 28701; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Minutes: Board of Directors)
      - Minutes: Board of Directors, 23 August 1973; 28702; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Minutes: Board of Directors)
      - Minutes: Board of Directors, 29 November 1973; 28703; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Minutes: Board of Directors)
      - Minutes: Executive Committee, 1973-1975; 28704; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Minutes: Executive Committee)
      - Minutes, 1973-1976; 28705; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Minutes)
      - Minutes: Board of Directors, 21 February 1974; 28706; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Minutes: Board of Directors)
      - Minutes: Board of Directors, 29-30 August 1974; 28707; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Minutes: Board of Directors)
      - Minutes: Board of Directors, 20 September 1974; 28708; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Minutes: Board of Directors)
      - Minutes: Board of Directors, 15 November 1974; 28709; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Minutes: Board of Directors)
      - Minutes: Board of Directors, 3 January 1975; 28710; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Minutes: Board of Directors)
      - Minutes: Board of Directors, 21 February 1975; 28711; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Minutes: Board of Directors)
      - Minutes: Executive Committee, 21 March 1975; 28712; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Minutes: Executive Committee)
      - Minutes: Board of Directors, 30 May 1975; 28713; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Minutes: Board of Directors)
      - Minutes: Board of Directors, 31 October 1975; 28714; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Minutes: Board of Directors)
      - Miscellaneous, 1950-1951; 28715; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Miscellaneous)
      - Miscellaneous, 1956-1957; 28716; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Miscellaneous)
      - Miscellaneous, 1970-1975; 28717; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Miscellaneous)
      - Miscellaneous Current, December 1976; 28718; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Miscellaneous Current)
      - Miscellaneous - Hold for Future, 1957; 35194; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Miscellaneous - Hold for Future)
      - National Lead Company, 1954; 28719; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder National Lead Company)
      - N. Elton Aydlett Files, 1952-1985; 7027; Stick, David, 1919-2009
        - Aydlett, N. Elton, 1959-1973; 28720; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Aydlett, N. Elton)
        - Blocks 34-37, circa 1972; 28721; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Blocks 34-37)
        - Bylaws, 1971-1972; 28722; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Bylaws)
        - Circle Drive Deeds, 1973; 28723; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Circle Drive Deeds)
        - Composite Plat, 1972; 28724; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Composite Plat)
        - Confidential, 1972; 28725; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Confidential)
        - Contracts, 1972; 28726; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Contracts)
        - Deeds: J. MacN Duff, 1972; 28727; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Deeds: J. MacN Duff)
        - Directors, 15 December 1970; 28728; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Directors)
        - Executive Committee, 1971; 28729; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Executive Committee)
        - Hasserot Property Deed, 1974; 28730; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Hasserot Property Deed)
        - HUD [Housing and Urban Development], 1972; 28731; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder HUD [Housing and Urban Development])
        - Mineral Rights, 1953-1972; 28732; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Mineral Rights)
        - Purported Agreements, Blocks 170, 175, and 84, 1971; 28733; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Purported Agreements, Blocks 170, 175, and 84)
        - Rocket Removal, 1972; 28734; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Rocket Removal)
        - Signatures on Contracts, 1971; 28735; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Signatures on Contracts)
        - Southern Shores Realty Company Agreement, 1972; 28736; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Southern Shores Realty Company Agreement)
        - Tax Problems, 1970-1972; 28737; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Tax Problems)
        - Title Insurance, 1969-1972; 28738; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Title Insurance)
        - White Hall and Mullen, 1972; 28739; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder White Hall and Mullen)
      - Notes (DCH, Inc.), 1978-1985; 28740; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Notes (DCH, Inc.))
      - Owen, K. Elizabeth, 1952-1953; 28741; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Owen, K. Elizabeth)
      - Parker, Mrs. Sally C., Jackson, N.C., 1953; 28742; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Parker, Mrs. Sally C., Jackson, N.C.)
      - Pension and Profit Sharing Plan, 1976; 28743; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Pension and Profit Sharing Plan)
      - Personal Files, 1951-1976; 7028; Stick, David, 1919-2009
        - Advertising, 1975; 28744; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Advertising)
        - Aydlett, Cyrus, 1975; 28745; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Aydlett, Cyrus)
        - Balance Sheets Rev. by David Stick, 1964-1974; 28746; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Balance Sheets Rev. by David Stick)
        - Biggs Report, 1973; 28747; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Biggs Report)
        - Bylaws, Charters, etc., 1951-1972; 28748; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Bylaws, Charters, etc.)
        - Cashflow, 1972-1975; 28749; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Cashflow)
        - Chicahauk Associations, 1974-1975; 28750; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Chicahauk Associations)
        - Chicahauk Promotions, 1974; 28751; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Chicahauk Promotions)
        - Collapsibility, 1973-1975; 28752; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Collapsibility)
        - Confidential Reports, 1956-1975; 28753; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Confidential Reports)
        - Contingency Plans, 1975-1976; 28754; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Contingency Plans)
        - Filing System, 1974; 28755; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Filing System)
        - Hauck - Old Duck Road, 1976; 28756; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Hauck - Old Duck Road)
        - Long Range Projections, 1970; 28757; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Long Range Projections)
        - Lot Inventories, 1972; 28758; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Lot Inventories)
        - Management Study, 1972; 28759; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Management Study)
        - McMullan, Brock, 1975-1976; 28760; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder McMullan, Brock)
        - Meadows, Frank, 1969-1971; 28761; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Meadows, Frank)
        - Miscellaneous, 1974-1976; 28762; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Miscellaneous)
        - Newsletter, 1969-1975; 28763; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Newsletter)
        - Property Owner Problems, 1975-1976; 28764; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Property Owner Problems)
        - Property Owners Data, 1973-1974; 28765; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Property Owners Data)